A Guide to the Fritz Albert Lipmann papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA123
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Manuscripts and Notes, 1930-1985; 4; 17 Cubic Feet
  - Sulfate reduction by chick yolk sac (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Sulfate transfer, 1 of 2 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Sulfate transfer, 2 of 2 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Succinyl phosphate (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Sulfate (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Sulfate esters (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Sulfate reduction, 1 of 2 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Sulfate reduction, 2 of 2 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Sulfate transferring enzymes (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Summary of experiments (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Symposium on amino acid activation (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Synthesis de L'Acide Cysteique (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Synthesis and cofactor activity (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Synthesis of bacteriophage (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Synthesis of guanosine, 1 of 2 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Synthesis of guanosine, 2 of 2 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Synthesis of guanosine tetraphosphate (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Synthesis of phage-specifice (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Synthesis of phosphoryl-enolphruvate (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Synthesis of serum proteins (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Synthesis of template RNA (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Thyroxine material (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - TIBS paper (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Transfer from RNA to microsome (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Transfer RNA (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Transfer of sulfate (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Transfer of sulfate among phenolia compounds (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Transmethylation, 1 of 4 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Transmethylation, 2 of 4 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Transmethylation, 3 of 4 (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Transmethylation, 4 of 4 (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - Transport of D-glucose (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Trends in biochemistry (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Twenty years of molecular biology (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Two Albert Frenkel papers (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Two Carbamyl phosphate methods (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Tyrocidine biosynthesis, 1 of 2 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Tyrocidine biosynthesis, 2 of 2 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Tyrocidine synthesis, 1 of 2 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Tyrocidine synthesis, 2 of 2 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Tyrocidine and sporulation (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Tyr-phosphorylation of pig heart (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Uncoupling of respiration and phosphorylation (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Unexpected implication of phosphate in pyruvic (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Unusual nucleotide polyphosphates, 1 of 2 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Unusual nucleotide polyphosphates, 2 of 2 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Valinomycin biosynthesis (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Valinomycin study (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Vienna abstracts (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Viral RNA and the genetic code (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Vitamin chapter (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Vitamin chapter copies and miscellaneous material (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Wanderings of a Biochemist book gallery, 1 of 3 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Wanderings of a Biochemist book gallery, 2 of 3 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Wanderings of a Biochemist book gallery, 3 of 3 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Wanderings of a Biochemist final draft, 1 of 3 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Wanderings of a Biochemist final draft, 2 of 3 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Wanderings of a Biochemist final draft, 3 of 3 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Wanderings of a Biochemist master copy, 1 of 3 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Wanderings of a Biochemist master copy, 2 of 3 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Wanderings of a Biochemist master copy, 3 of 3 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - What do we know about protein synthesis (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - What is a scientist?, 1 of 2 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - What is a scientist?, 2 of 2 (Box 100, Folder 11)
- Laboratory Files, 1930-1985; 5; 10 Cubic Feet
  Information on grants and grant applications, notes on laboratory experiments, receipts for laboratory purchases and travel expenses, records of laboratory personnel and students.
  - Acetate transfer (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Acetyl glucosamine (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Acetylation of amino acids (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Acetylation on paper chromatogram (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Activation of photophosphorylation (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Alcohol dehydrogenase (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Alumni of laboratory (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Amino acid oxidase II (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Ammonium sulfate solutions (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Annual review of intramural research (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Applicants' curriculum vitae (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Applications to work in laboratory A-L, 1 of 3 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Applications to work in laboratory A-L, 2 of 3 (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - Applications to work in laboratory A-L, 3 of 3 (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - Applications to work in laboratory M-Z, 1 of 3 (Box 101, Folder 15)
  - Applications to work in laboratory M-Z, 2 of 3 (Box 101, Folder 16)
  - Applications to work in laboratory M-Z, 3 of 3 (Box 101, Folder 17)
  - Applications to work in laboratory, 1970-1971; 1 of 2 (Box 101, Folder 18)
  - Applications to work in laboratory, 1970-1971; 2 of 2 (Box 101, Folder 19)
  - Applications to work in laboratory, 1972-1973; 1 of 2 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Applications to work in laboratory, 1972-1973; 2 of 2 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Autograph requests (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Bacterial spore (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Batya (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Bessman symposium (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Biochemistry study section reports, 1963 September (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Biological sulfate activation and transfer (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Biology 195 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Bio-raol laboratories model (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Biosynthesis of chondroitin (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - Budget (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - Buffers (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - Calcium phosphate gel (Box 102, Folder 14)
  - Carbamyl phosphate (Box 102, Folder 15)
  - Carl F Cori materials, 1 of 2 (Box 102, Folder 16)
  - Carl F Cori materials, 2 of 2 (Box 102, Folder 17)
  - Carnegie-Mellon, Pittsburgh, 1981 (Box 102, Folder 18)
  - Chemical aspects of protein synthesis, 1 of 5 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Chemical aspects of protein synthesis, 2 of 5 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Chemical aspects of protein synthesis, 3 of 5 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Chemical aspects of protein synthesis, 4 of 5 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Chemical aspects of protein synthesis, 5 of 5 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Chondroitin sulfate (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Circe effect, 1 of 2 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Circe effect, 2 of 2 (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Citrate Synthesis by enzyme (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Clippings (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - CoA synthesizing enzymes (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - Coenzyme A Assay (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - Cori bioessays (Box 103, Folder 13)
  - Current personnel (Box 103, Folder 14)
  - Curriculum vitae material (Box 103, Folder 15)
  - Cystein oxidalia (Box 103, Folder 16)
  - Dallas symposium (Box 103, Folder 17)
  - dCMP deaminase assay (Box 103, Folder 18)
  - Determination notes (Box 103, Folder 19)
  - Development of the acetylation problem (Box 103, Folder 20)
  - Diphosphofructose aldolase (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Drug research (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Efforts reports, 1974-1975; 1 of 2 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Efforts reports, 1974-1975; 2 of 2 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Efforts reports, 1978-1980; 1 of 2 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Efforts reports, 1978-1980; 2 of 2 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Efforts reports, 1982-1983; 1 of 2 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Efforts reports, 1982-1983; 2 of 2 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Efforts reports, 1984; 1 of 3 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Efforts reports, 1984; 1 of 3 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Efforts reports, 1984; 1 of 3 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Eightieth birthday, Paris, 1979 July; 1 of 2 (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Eightieth birthday, Paris, 1979 July; 2 of 2 (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - Eighty-fifth birthday symposium, Japan, 1984 May (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - Enzyme interactions (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Enzymatic synthesis of thiamine (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Expense accounts (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Experimental physik (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - FEBS programme (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Federation meetings, 1956 April 16-20 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Federation meeting material, 1957 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Formation of a tryptophan ATP ester (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Formation of methylglyox in coli preparations (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Francois Chapeville (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Funds, 1 of 3 (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Funds, 2 of 3 (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Funds, 3 of 3 (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - Gesellschaft der freunde (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Giessen Germany meeting (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Giva tayim (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Glucose (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Glucose micro method (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Glucose transport (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Glycolysis (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Gordon conference Tilton New Hampshire, 1981 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Grant application number 13972 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Grant-Cancer Institute (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Grant-National Cancer Institute application, 1 of 2 (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - Grant-National Cancer Institute application, 2 of 2 (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Grants and fellowships (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - Handbook of radioactivity and tracer methodology, 1 of 5 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Handbook of radioactivity and tracer methodology, 2 of 5 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Handbook of radioactivity and tracer methodology, 3 of 5 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Handbook of radioactivity and tracer methodology, 4 of 5 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Handbook of radioactivity and tracer methodology, 5 of 5 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - High energy papers (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Hildebrand thesis, 1 of 3 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Hildebrand thesis, 2 of 3 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Hildebrand thesis, 3 of 3 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Holland forum (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Hormone experiments (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Housing (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Humboldt award (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - Hydrazones, total (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - Institute de la Vie, 1980 March (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - Institute de la Vie, Brussels, 1978 May 17-22 (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - Insurance policies, 1 of 2 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Insurance policies, 2 of 2 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Intermediary metabolism of fishes (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - IOPAB symposium (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Isolation of a glucose transport protein (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Issues, 1967-1968 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Jose Sy-Miscellaneous (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Jose Sy, 1 of 2 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Jose Sy, 2 of 2 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Kamen sixty-fifth birthday symposium, 1978 August (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - Karl Ernst von Baer (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Kiel, 1982 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Kleinkauf symposium (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Laboratory data control (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Laboratory equipment service contracts, 1 of 2 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Laboratory equipment service contracts, 2 of 2 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Laboratory notebook, number one, unidentified (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Laboratory notebook, number two, unidentified (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Laboratory notebook, number three, unidentified (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Laboratory notebook-Assay method of NPS and DNAs (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Laboratory notebook-Biochemical Research Laboratory (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Laboratory notebook-Biochemical Research Laboratory, 1952 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Laboratory notebook-charts (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Laboratory notebook-DHA enzyme (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Laboratory notebook-DNP, 1 of 3 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Laboratory notebook-DNP, 2 of 3 (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Laboratory notebook-DNP, 3 of 3 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Laboratory notebook-electrophoresis (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Laboratory notebook-fluoride (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Laboratory notebook-Glucose, 1 of 2 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Laboratory notebook-Glucose, 2 of 2 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Laboratory notebook-Klein (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Laboratory notebook-lactic acid (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Laboratory notebook-lactic acid formation (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Laboratory notebook-maloncite, embryonic heart (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Laboratory notebook-Massachusetts General Hospital (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Laboratory notebook-metabolism (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Laboratory notebook-Nierneyer (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Laboratory notebook-number one, Lorentz Engstrom (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Laboratory notebook-number two, Lorentz Engstrom (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Laboratory notebook-number three, Lorentz Engstrom (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Laboratory notebook-QO2 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Laboratory notebook-R. Flynn (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Laboratory notebook-R. Flynn Book 7, 1 of 3 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Laboratory notebook-R. Flynn Book 7, 2 of 3 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Laboratory notebook-R. Flynn Book 7, 3 of 3 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Laboratory notebook-R. Flynn Book 8, 1 of 3 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Laboratory notebook-R. Flynn Book 8, 2 of 3 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Laboratory notebook-R. Flynn Book 8, 3 of 3 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Laboratory notebook-radioactive experiments, 1943 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Laboratory notebook-recovery of CoA, 1951-1952 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Laboratory notebook-Soodak's experiment (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - Laboratory notebook-[sulfate] (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1918 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1928 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1929 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1929 September 6-1930 January 25 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1930-1932 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1932 October-1933 February (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1933 August-1934 January (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1934-1935 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1937 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1938 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1938 November (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1939 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1939-1940 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1939-1946 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1940 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1940s (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1941 January-1942 March (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1942 September (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1942-1943 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1942 September-1943 March (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1943; 1 of 2 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1943; 2 of 2 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1944; 1 of 2 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1944; 2 of 2 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1946 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1947; 1 of 2 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1947; 2 of 2 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1947 May 3 1947 December 22 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1948 February-July (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1949 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1950; 1 of 2 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1950; 2 of 2 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1950 January-July (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1950 July-August (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1951 June-July (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1952 November-1953 March (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1953-1954 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1957-1958 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Laboratory notebook, 1959-1960 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Laboratory phosphate (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Laboratory regulations (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - L-lactate in normal cell (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Lee review (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Lindau, 1981 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Lindau Nobel meeting, 1978 June 26-30 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Lippmann curriculum (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Lipmann research proposals, 1964-1965 (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Lipmann symposium (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Locatio, Spring 1963 (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Markle fellowship (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Martinique meetings (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Mathematiques (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Mi Cheh Liu (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, 1 of 3 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, 2 of 3 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous, 3 of 3 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Mitochondrial-specific aminoacyl-RNA (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Molecular weights and Pka values (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Monumenta Nipponica (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Mt. Allison University, Canada (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Mukai, Dr. Jun-Ichiro (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - Myasthenia Clinic (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - N. Blixenkrone-Moller (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - NIH manpower questionnaire (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - NIH symposium, 1984 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Nobel Laureates meeting, 1984 June (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Nobel Prize nominations, 1 of 2 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Nobel Prize nominations, 2 of 2 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Nomenclature-Waldo Cohn (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - NSF grant at Rockefeller Foundation (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - NSF grant, 1970; 1 of 2 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - NSF grant, 1970; 2 of 2 (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - NSF grant, 1973 (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - NSF grant, 1980-1982 (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - Oversigt over Selskabets Virksomhed (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Oxalacetic acid (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Palmetto pigeon plant (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Past personnel (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Permanent reprint list (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Personnel-current, 1 of 2 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Personnel-current, 2 of 2 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Personnel, 1982-1986 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Personnel matters-faculty list change (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Personnel matters-forms, various (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - Personnel-past (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - Phosphorus, total (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Philip Handler (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Prentice-Hall (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Preparation notes (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Protein and nucleic acid (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Protein biosynthesis in historical perspective (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Public Health Service study section, 1 of 3 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Public Health Service study section, 2 of 3 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Public Health Service study section, 3 of 3 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Polyamino acids as protein models, 1 of 5 (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - Polyamino acids as protein models, 2 of 5 (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - Polyamino acids as protein models, 3 of 5 (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - Polyamino acids as protein models, 4 of 5 (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - Polyamino acids as protein models, 5 of 5 (Box 123, Folder 14)
  - Radioactive isotopes-regulations (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Ravello meeting-September 2-15, 1963 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Recent excitement in the coding problem (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Reprint mailing list (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Ribonuclease-free ribosomes from E. Coli (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Rozen, Elizabeth-Laboratory assistant (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Rules for publication (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Rutgers symposium (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller Institute-budget, 1 of 2 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Rockefeller Institute-budget, 2 of 2 (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Rockefeller Institute-miscellaneous (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Rockefeller Institute-Quarterly (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - Rockefeller Institute-talk to trustees, 1958 (Box 124, Folder 13)
  - Rockefeller University annual reports, 1 of 2 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller University annual reports, 2 of 2 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller University budget (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller University catalogue (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller general information, 1 of 2 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller general information, 2 of 2 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller University miscellaneous (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller University personnel forms (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Science and Nature advertisements (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Science and technology (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Scientific and educational programs (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Simpson, Melvin (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Slaughter house permit (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - South American trip, 1963; 1 of 2 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - South American trip, 1963; 2 of 2 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - Space research, 1 of 3 (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - Space research, 2 of 3 (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - Space research, 3 of 3 (Box 126, Folder 10)
  - Srere (Box 126, Folder 11)
  - Stereochemistry (Box 126, Folder 12)
  - Strasbourg, France, 1981 September 20 (Box 126, Folder 13)
  - Student information, 1 of 3 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Student information, 2 of 3 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - Student information, 3 of 3 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Student information 2, 1 of 2 (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Student information 2, 2 of 2 (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Student seminar, 1962 December; 1 of 2 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Student seminar, 1962 December; 2 of 2 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Sturtevant, Dr. Julian M. (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Subscriptions (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Suiko, Dr. Masahito (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Sulfate activation (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Sulfate transfer (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Texas and Florida meetings, 1980 March 20-26 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Theater and the university (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - Toyoda, Dr. Yukiyasu (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - Transcript specificity fractionation (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Traut thesis (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Travel expense sheets, 1954 (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - Travel expenses (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - Travel information, 1958 (Box 128, Folder 8)
  - Tyrosine-o-sulfate (Box 128, Folder 9)
  - Über die Prozesse (Box 128, Folder 10)
  - Undersogelser Over (Box 128, Folder 11)
  - United States Public Health Service [USPHS] Grant (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - USPHS Grant, 1966-1967; 1 of 2 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - USPHS Grant, 1966-1967; 2 of 2 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - USPHS Grant, 1967-1968 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - USPHS Grant, 1968-1969 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - USPHS Grant, 1969-1970 (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - USPHS Grant, 1970-1971; 1 of 2 (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - USPHS Grant, 1970-1971; 2 of 2 (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - USPHS Grant, 1971-1973; 1 of 2 (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - USPHS Grant, 1971-1973; 2 of 2 (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - USPHS Grant, 1972-1973 (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - USPHS Grant, 1973-1974 (Box 129, Folder 12)
  - USPHS Grant, 1974-1975 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - USPHS Grant, 1975-1976 (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - USPHS Grant, 1976-1977 (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - USPHS Grant, 1977-1978; 1 of 2 (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - USPHS Grant, 1977-1978; 2 of 2 (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - USPHS Grant, 1978-1979 (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - USPHS Grant, 1980 (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - USPHS Grant request for Rockefeller Institute (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - Virtis freezer-dryer, 1984 (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Walsh thesis, 1 of 3 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Walsh thesis, 2 of 3 (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Walsh thesis, 3 of 3 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Wang, Hwei-Xun (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Welch Foundation (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Workshops on shock, 1962 June 19; 1 of 2 (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - Workshops on shock, 1962 June 19; 2 of 2 (Box 131, Folder 8)
- Professional Societies, 1957-1979; 6; 6 Cubic Feet
  Correspondence, literature of various academic professional societies, notes from society meetings, peer reviews of numerous scientific articles.
  - Academic Press (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - American Cancer Society-Council for Research and Clinical Investigation Awards1 of 2 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - American Cancer Society-Council for Research and Clinical Investigation Awards2 of 2 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - American Cancer Society grant applications (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - American Cancer Society grant renewals (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - American Chemical Society meeting (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - American Chemical Society, 1965-1966 (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - American Chemical Society, 1967-1969 (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - American Chemical Society, 1968 (Box 132, Folder 9)